

kate.vonhouck.com

@ kate4china@gmail.com

**&** (425)449-0838

## **SKILLS**

#### Software

Sketch

Figma

Invision

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Indesign

Adobe Illustrator

**Adobe After Effects** 

Adobe Premiere

HTML/CSS

Java Script

Swift

## Design

Storyboarding

Persona

Wireframing

Prototyping

#### Research

**User Interviews** 

**Usability Testing** 

**Competitive Analisies** 

## **OBJECTIVE**

Hey, Kate here. I am a junior designer excited to continue in the world of design. I'm passionate about research, user testing and user-oriented design for websites and mobile apps. I like to focus on making great looking and fluid interfaces that feel natural and obvious to use. Check out my portfolio to see projects I have completed recently.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Freelance Visual Designer**

San Francisco, CA | August 2018 - Present

Visual designer at Reclinerpool:

· logo design & icon design

# Freelance UX/UI Designer

San Francisco, CA | May 2018 - Present

UX/UI designer for Istrolid 2 computer game:

- visual design for game interfaces
- experience design for the main menu and widgets
- hierarchy of game screens

#### Gravitational Inc / UX Consultant

Oakland, CA | October 2017 - April 2018

Primary designer at Gravitational Inc:

- UX/UI design for open source documentation site
- · company logo and product logos
- visual design language with a full icon set
- unified navigation system
- technical and marketing diagrams

# Languages

**English** 

Russian

Chinese

#### **Personal**

Creativity

Organization

Team Player

Commitment

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Academy of Art University**

Bachelor of Web Design & New Media
San Francisco, CA | January 2014 - May 2017

# City College of San Francisco, San Francosco, CA

General Education in Business

San Francisco, CA | January 2011 - May 2014

### **Bellevue College**

Certificate in English Program

Bellevue, WA | January 2010 - June 2011

#### **Altai State University**

Associate of Asian Studies

Barnaul, Russia | September 2007 - May 2009